George S. McGovern Papers Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1957-1984 (bulk 1968-1972 )
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1957-1984; 105.42 linear feet 110 boxes Approximately 1,785 items
  - Subseries 5C, 1970-1984 February 22; 30.4 linear feet 32 boxes
    - 1972, portion of 379 boxes
      - Primary Day-Manchester, New Hampshire, 1972 February 22; 1314; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Clearwater, Florida and Neighbors, 1972 February 27; 756; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Radio, 1972 February 27; 796; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV/Radio, 1972 February 28; 797; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Buses to Schools, 1972 February 29; 798; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV/Radio Capsules, 1972 March 1; 162; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Whistle Stop Train Trip Through California, 1972 March 6; 147; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV Capsules, New Hampshire Primary, 1972 March 6; 161; 1 box (Box 817)
      - 1972 March 6, 773; 1 box (Box 817)
      - New Hampshire Primary Results, CBS, NBC, ABC TV Specials; CBS Radio; NET TV Report, 1972 March 7; 1746; 1 box (Box 817)
      - CBS TV McGovern/Muskie, 1972 March 8; 772; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 March 12; 160; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Press Conference, Milwaukee, 1972 March 16-22; 1211; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Victor Reuther, Racine, Wisconsin, 1972 March 18; 1313; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV, 1972 March 2; 799; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Labor Reception, Springfield, Illinois, 1972 March 20; 1311; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Northern Illinois University, 1972 March 20; 1320; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV, 1972 March 23; 775; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Wisconsin, 1972 March 23; 1359; 1 box (Box 817)
      - University Stout-ME Nominee, 1972 March 23; 1360; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Democrats TV Ads, 1972 March 24; 774; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Teachers' Speech, Milwaukee, 1972 March 24; 886; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Wibrocton Paper, 1972 March 26; 1538; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV, 1972 March 27; 776; 1 box (Box 817)
      - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1972 March 27; 1219; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Rockville Speech and Green Bay High School Discussion, 1972 March 28; 1214; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Kenosha Paper Press Conference, 1972 March 28-29; 1315; 1 box (Box 817)
      - McGovern, 1972 March 29; 771; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Original Campaign Music, 1972 March 29; 791; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Bay Port High School, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1972 March 29; 893; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Boston Press Conference/Fall River Firestone Workers, 1972 April 1; 134; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Brockton High School, Massachusetts, 1972 April 1; 137; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Speech at Wisconsin Rally, 1972 April 1; 755; 1 box (Box 817)
      - McGovern, 1972 April 1; 770; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Massachusetts Primary, Aerospace Speech, Boston, 1972 April 1; 877; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV Capsules-Candidates and Wives, 1972 April 3-5; 1233; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Metro Media TV, 1972 April 5; 769; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Victory Statement, Wisconsin, 1972 April 4; 1747; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Wisconsin Primary Results, ABC, CBS, NBC, 1972 April 4; 1748; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Issues and Answers and TV Capsules, 1972 April 5; 895; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Mrs. McGovern, 1972 April 5; 1558; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV Capsule-Washington Review, 1972 April 6-8; 1234; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV, 1972 April 10; 768; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV, 1972 April 11; 779; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV, 1972 April 12; 777; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Sugar, 1972 April 19; 892; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 April 21-23; 154; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Knights of Columbus, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1972 April 23; 884; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Chet Huntley Show, 1972 April 24; 1375; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Massachusetts and Pennsylvania Primary Results, NBC, ABC, CBS, NET, 1972 April 24; 1749; 1 box (Box 817)
      - The Day After Pennsylvania and Massachusetts, 1972 April 26; 1750; 1 box (Box 818)
      - Taxes, G.E. Plant, 1972 April 28; 780; 1 box (Box 818)
      - Bond Endorsement, Cleveland, 1972 April 29; 1197; 25 minutes (Box 818)
      - Youngstown Rally, Akron Rally, 1972 April 30; 1623; 1 box (Box 818)
      - Debate of 5 Candidates #1, 1972 May 3; 754; 1 box (Box 818)
      - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Omaha, 1972 May 5; 1596; 1 box (Box 818)
      - Northern California Labor for McGovern, 1972 May 15; 1593; 1 box (Box 818)
      - McGovern and Chavez, Mrs. McGovern, 1972 May 19; 781; 1 box (Box 818)
      - San Francisco, 1972 May 20; 1317; 1 box (Box 818)
      - "30 Minutes," NET TV Guest; "Election ’72 Delegates," NET TV; Oregon and Rhode Island Primary, ABC, 1972 May 23-25; 1751; 1 box (Box 818)
      - McGovern Bio, 1972 May 26; 1; 28 minutes 20 seconds 16mm (Box 818)
      - McGovern 1/2-hour Discussion Show, 1972 May 26; 14; 2-inch 1 box (Box 819)
      - California, 1972 May 26; 876; 1 box (Box 820)
      - McGovern/Humphrey Debate, Face the Nation, 1972 May 28; 1363; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV, 1972 May 30; 782; 1 box (Box 820)
      - McGovern/Humphrey, Meet the Press Debate, 1972 May 30; 1349; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Image Politics Election, 1972 May 31; 155; 1 box (Box 820)
      - International Service Employees' Union, San Francisco, 1972 May 31; 1585; 1 box (Box 820)
      - McGovern, 1972 June 2-4; 157; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 June 6; 158; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Policy Panel on Crime and Justice, 1972 June 6; 1594; 1 box (Box 820)
      - California Primary, 2 A.M. Reports, CBS, NBC, 1972 June 6; 1752; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules; California Primary, NBC; NET TV Interviews, 1972 June 6; 1753; 1 box (Box 820)
      - California Primary, TV Capsules, 1972 June 7; 1659; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 June 9; 159; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Washington Week Review, 1972 June 10; 1357; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 June 12-13; 146; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Albany Rally, 1972 June 13; 1296; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Election '72-Women's Vote, 1972 June 14; 1269; 1 box (Box 820)
      - New York and Democrats, 1972 June 15; 152; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Our Own Nation, 1972 June 16; 38 seconds (Box 820)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 783, 784.
      - TV Coverages, 1972 June 16-20; 1754; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Women's Democratic Club, 1972 June 17; 1212; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Coverages; "Election ’72," NET TV; Biographies of McGovern, HHH, Other TV, 1972 June 20-21; 1755; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Muskie on Issues and Answers and Humphrey on Face the Nation, 1972 June 23-25; 1355; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Oklahoma City Rally, 1972 June 25; 1559; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Democrats on McGovern, Matthew-Troy Interview, 1972 June 25-26; 1238; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Of the Population, 1972 June 26; 767; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Upstate New York and Michigan, 1972 June 26; 1200; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 June 27; 151; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Democrats, 1972 June 28; 150; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Including CBS Interview, 1972 June 29-30; 130; 16mm 1 box (Box 820)
      - Come to Hate, 1972 June 29; 759; 49 seconds (Box 820)
      - Issues and Answers, 1972 June 30; 1356; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Patricia Harris on Face the Nation and Richard Neustadt on Meet the Press, 1972 July 2; 1402; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Democrats...McGovern, 1972 July 3-4; 1172; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Democrats, 1972 July 5; 1663; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Democrats TV Capsules, 1972 July 7-11; 1644; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Reports, 1972 July 6; 1666; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Dellums-Mankiewicz, 1972 July 9; 1310; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Meet the Press, McGovern, Humphrey, Muskie, Chisholm, Jackson, 1972 July 9; 1354; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Miami, 1972 July 11-12; portion of 1 box (Box 820)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1645, 1646.
      - TV, 1972 July 14; 1647; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Election '72, Nixon-McGovern-Democrats, 1972 July 14; 1664; 1 box (Box 820)
      - The Week McGovern Won, CBS TV Special, 1972 July 16; 1340; 1 box (Box 820)
      - The Week McGovern Won, CBS TV Special, 1972 July 16; 1341; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Richard Wade Interview, Victor Gotbaum Interview, 1972 July 16; 1648; 1 box (Box 820)
      - The Race, 1972 July 18; 760; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 July 18; 1665; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Period of Time, 1972 July 20; 762; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Larry O'Brien Today Interview, 1972 July 21; 1656; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Washington Week Review, 1972 July 22; 1669; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Face the Nation, Thomas Eagleton Issues and Meet the Press-John Connally, 1972 July 22-23; 867; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Campaign '72, Problems McGovern Will Face, CBS TV, 1972 July 23; 1346; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV/FM, 1972 July 24; 761; 1 box (Box 820)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 July 25; 1668; 1 box (Box 820)
      - Pat Donovan's Collection, 1972 July 26; 1342; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern-Eagleton, 1972 July 26; 1350; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern-Eagleton, 1972 July 27; 1345; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsule Reports, 1972 July 28; 1237; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern-Eagleton Special, Face the Nation, 1972 July 29; 1339; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Next November, 1972 July 30; 778; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Newslight, Richard Wade, NBC TV, 1972 July 30; 1667; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern/Eagleton Press Conference, 1972 July 31; 1343; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsules and Convention Highlights, 1972 July 31; 1655; 1 box (Box 821)
      - AFT Speech, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1972 August; 1400; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Eagleton Interviews, CBS and Today, 1972 August 1; 1348; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Campaign '72, 1972 August 6; 1263; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern-Shriver, 1972 August 7-8; 1347; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern-Shriver Vice President Convention, 1972 August 8; 1261; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Amalgamated Meat-Cutters' Union, 1972 August 8; 1388; 1 box (Box 821)
      - After Wallace, What?, Election '72, 1972 August 10; 1344; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Issues and Answers McGovern and Face the Nation Sargeant Shriver, The Perils of Polling, 1972 August 13; 868; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Ohio, 1972 August 15; 1389; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Springfield, Illinois, 1972 August 16; 1406; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Peoria-Statements on McGovern, 1972 August 16-17; 1236; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 August 18-24; 1642; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern in Texas, 1972 August 21; 1401; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Face the Nation Mankiewicz/Hart Interview and Richard Nixon Addresses the Legionaires, 1972 August 23-25; 866; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Labor Speech, 1972 August 24; 1319; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Labor Speech, 1972 August 25; 1300; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Washington Press Conference, 1972 August 28; 1307; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 August 28; 1675; 1 box (Box 821)
      - New York City, 1972 August 29; 1392; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern at Wall Street, 1972 August 29; 1643; 1 box (Box 821)
      - #1 Public Service Jobs, 1972 August 30; 788; 1 box (Box 821)
      - New York Board of Rabbis, Conference of Soviet Jewry, 1972 August 30; 852; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern on Today, 1972 August 30; 1358; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 August 31; 1676; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Baltimore Press Conference, 1972 September; 1525; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Sioux Falls Airport Rally, 1972 September 1; 1182; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 1; 1672; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern TV, 1972 September 3; 763; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Campaign Financing, CBS Special, 1972 September 3; 1640; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Ohio, Labor Day, 1972 September 4; 1186; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Washington Street, 1972 September 4; 1218; 1 box (Box 821)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 4; 1673; 1 box (Box 821)
      - Vietnam Veteran on Jerry Williams, 1972 September 4; 1674; 1 box (Box 821)
      - McGovern Vets, 1972 September 6; 18; 4 minutes 16 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 821)
      - McGovern: Mrs. Clark, Mr. Cook, Mr. Cubby, 1972 September 6; 25; 60 seconds 2-inch (Box 822)
      - Eleanor McGovern with Dinah, NBC TV, 1972 September 7; 1362; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Senator McGovern on Daley Meeting and Endorsement, 1972 September 8; 766; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Washington Week Review, 1972 September 8; 1641; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Flint, Michigan/Columbus, Ohio, 1972 September 9; 889; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules and Sargeant Shriver on Issues and Answers, 1972 September 9-10; 894; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Farmfest, Minnesota, 1972 September 11; 1213; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 11; 1678; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 12; 1677; 1 box (Box 822)
      - McGovern: Court #5, 1972 September 13; 60; 5 minutes 2-inch color) (Box 822)
      - McGovern-Kennedy, 1972 September 13; 1545; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 13-14; 1671; 1 box (Box 822)
      - 6 spots, local station, 1972 September 14; 58; 2-inch color) 1 box (Box 822)
      - Abe Ribicoff on McGovern, 30 minutes, 1972 September 15; 1171; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules, See How They Run, 1972 September 15-17; 1638; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Inflation Speech Portland, Maine and Marshall University, Huntington, West Virginia, 1972 September 15-17; 758; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Logan, West Virginia/Carbondale, Illinois, 1972 September 18; 757; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Today, Shriver Interview, 1972 September 18; 1361; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Sioux Falls Airport Handshaking, 1972 September 18; 1539; 1 box (Box 822)
      - San Francisco, Reception and Speech in Chicago, 1972 September 19-25; 1524; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 20; 890; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Speech on Munich, 1972 September 20; 1544; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Vietnam, Philadelphia, 1972 September 20; 1580; 1 box (Box 822)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 21; 891; 1 box (Box 822)
      - National Defense Policy Debate, 1972 September 21; 1526; 1 box (Box 822)
      - Moss and Stevenson Press Conference, 1972 September 21; 1586; 1 box (Box 822)
      - McGovern Family Farm, 1972 September 22; 65; 60 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 822)
      - The McGovern Girls on Today, 1972 September 22; 1 box (Box 823)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 879, 880, 1639.
      - Detroit-Labor Breakfast, 1972 September 22; 888; 1 box (Box 823)
      - World Press/Dole O'Brien on Issues and Answers and McGovern/Shriver/POW, 1972 September 22-24; 860; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Buckley-Mankiewicz, 1972 September 23-24; 1661; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Sioux Falls, 1972 September 24; 861; 1 box (Box 823)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 25; 859; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Seattle, 1972 September 25; 1536; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Campaign Pledge, 1972 September 26; 66; 30 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 823)
      - The Media and the Campaign, 1972 September 26; 1662; 1 box (Box 823)
      - TV Capsules and Net TV Election '72 County Chairman, 1972 September 27; 869; 1 box (Box 823)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 September 28; 850; 1 box (Box 823)
      - New York City-Abrams Testimonial, 1972 September 30; 887; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Baltimore City Fair, 1972 September 30; 849; 1 box (Box 823)
      - San Diego, 1972 October; 1397; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Des Moines, 1972 October; 1398; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Vietnam Speech, 1972 October; 1404; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Humphrey Endorses McGovern, 1972 October 1; 1196; 1 box (Box 823)
      - P.O.W. Wife, Southern California, 1972 October 1; 1297; 1 box (Box 823)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 October 2; 851; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Newark, New Jersey Military Rally, Lynhurst New Jersey, New York City Waldorf Astoria, 1972 October 2; 871; 1 box (Box 823)
      - UPI Editors Conference, 1972 October 2; 1384; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Behind the Lines, 1972 October 3; 1270; 1 box (Box 823)
      - McGovern/Black Press Corps Conference Call, 1972 October 3; 1370; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Niagara Falls, New York, 1972 October 3; 1399; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Liberal Party Dinner, New York City, 1972 October 4; 1396; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Liberal Party Speech, 1972 October 4; 1651; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Jewish Vote, Election '72, 1972 October 4; 1660; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Foreign Policy, Cleveland, 1972 October 5; 1579; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Shriver 30 minutes, TV Capsules, 1972 October 5; 1652; 1 box (Box 823)
      - The Advocates-McGovern Defense, 1972 October 6; 1271; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Polish Museum, Chicago, 1972 October 6; 1584; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Melvin Laird, Face the Nation, 1972 October 6-7; 1365; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Chicago Precinct Captain Luncheon, 1972 October 6-7; 1575; 1 box (Box 823)
      - TV/FM Capsules, 1972 October 9; 1179; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Michigan, 1972 October 9; 1193; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Senator Edward Muskie, Address before the City Club of Cleveland, 1972 October 9; 1204; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Michigan Speeches, 1972 October 10; 1183; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Chicago, 1972 October 10; 1188; 1 box (Box 823)
      - All About TV, 1972 October 10; 1264; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Vietnam TV, 1972 October 10; 1570; 1 box (Box 823)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 October 10; 1658; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Election '72: McGovern in Billings, 1972 October 11; 881; 1 box (Box 823)
      - McGovern at Wheaton, Maryland, 1972 October 11; 1379; 2 items (Box 823)
      - Boston Rally, 1972 October 11; 1394; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Erie, Pennsylvania, 1972 October 11; 1395; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Chicago Luncheon, 1972 October 11; 1588; 1 box (Box 823)
      - Local: Monopolies; Tax Shelters, 1972 October 12; 62; 60 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 824)
      - 4 Spots, 1972 October 12; 63; 60 seconds 2-inch (Box 824)
      - Ask Yourself; This Time, 1972 October 12; 69; 60 seconds 2-inch (Box 824)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 October 12; 1181; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Boston, 1972 October 12; 1187; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Minnesota University, 1972 October 12; 1566; 1 box (Box 824)
      - WCCO-TV, Minneapolis, 1972 October 12; 1581; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Cow Palace, San Francisco, 1972 October 13; 1 box (Box 824)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1189, 1190.
      - Meet the Press, Paul Warnake and Tax Reform:McGovern-Nixon, 1972 October 13-19; 1217; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Mrs. Terri Evers, 1972 October 14; 1546; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Los Angeles, 1972 October 15; 1569; 1 box (Box 824)
      - TV/FM Capsules, 1972 October 16; 1176; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Austin, Texas, 1972 October 16; 1405; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Shriver Interview and Black Journal, 1972 October 17; 1272; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Detroit, 1972 October 18; 1191; 1 box (Box 824)
      - TV Capsules, Election '72, 1972 October 18; 1273; 1 box (Box 824)
      - 1972 October 18, 1548; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Toledo, Ohio and Philadelphia, 1972 October 18-19; 1192; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Mankiewicz on 30 Minutes, 1972 October 19; 1274; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Alfred Smith Dinner, New York City, 1972 October 19; 1568; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Brooklyn, New York and New Jersey, 1972 October 19-20; 1194; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Hackensack, New Jersey, 1972 October 20; 865; 1 box (Box 824)
      - The Advocates, 1972 October 20; 1275; 1 box (Box 824)
      - McGovern, 1972 October 21; 723; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Bethlehem and Reading, Pennsylvania, 1972 October 21; 862; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1972 October 21; 863; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Pennsylvania Speeches, 1972 October 21; 864; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Sharp, Muskie, McGovern Speeches, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1972 October 21; 870; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Birmingham Dinner, 1972 October 21; 1583; 1 box (Box 824)
      - Issues and Answers/Sargeant Shriver on Face the Nation, 1972 October 22; 145; 1 box (Box 824)
      - 8 political spots; Special Interests, 1972 October 23; 52; 2-inch 1 box (Box 825)
        Topics include Watergate, unemployment, inflation, crime, Vietnam
      - Metromedia Phone Calls, 1972 October 23-24; 1654; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Atlanta Constitution, Election '72, 1972 October 25; 1268; 1 box (Box 826)
      - McGovern Morality Message, 1972 October 25; 1368; 28 minutes 30 seconds (Box 826)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 October 26; 854; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Iowa, Senator Hughes, 1972 October 26; 1572; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Advocates, 1972 October 27; 1276; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Meet the Press, 1972 October 29; 1216; 1 box (Box 826)
      - TV Capsules, Eunice Shriver on Today, 1972 October 30; 853; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Today Interview, 1972 October 31; 1208; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Speech, 1972 November 1; 1 box (Box 826)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1195, 1209.
      - Eleanor; Veterans, 1972 November 2; 71; 5 minutes 2-inch (Box 826)
      - Radio Spots, 1972 November 2; 1246; 1 box (Box 826)
      - McGovern Farm Speech. CBS Radio Network, 1972 November 2; 1385; 1 box (Box 826)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 November 2; 1649; 1 box (Box 826)
      - McGovern-Kennedy Endorsement, 1972 November 3; 49; 4 minutes 20 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 826)
      - McGovern: Hubert Humphrey, 1972 November 3; 70; 4 minutes 20 seconds 2-inch (Box 826)
      - Advocates, Nixon-McGovern, 1972 November 3; 1266; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Own Their Own Houses, 1972 November 31; 787; 1 box (Box 826)
      - All in the Family Episode, 1972 November 4; 617; U-Matic KC-60 1 box (Box 826)
      - Columbia Law School, 1972 November 4; 1567; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Shriver on Issues, Harris/Yankelovich, 1972 November 5; 883; 1 box (Box 826)
      - McGovern Network Speech, 1972 November 5; 1378; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Illinois/New York Rallies, 1972 November 5; 1407; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Vietnam, 1972 November 5; 1542; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Berlin, NH, 1972 November 5; 1563; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Campaign, 1972 November 6; 1650; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Draft Resisters Discussion on Today, 1972 November 6; 1657; 1 box (Box 826)
      - South Dakota, Election Day, 1972 November 7; 1557; 1 box (Box 826)
      - Taking Oath of Office, 1972 November 7; 1695; 1 box (Box 827)
      - TV Interviews, 1972 November 7-8; 1653; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Election 1972, 1972 November 8; 1262; 1 box (Box 827)
      - The Democrats, 1972 November 9; 1180; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Minnesota Kennedy Rally, 1972 November 9; 1574; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Washington Week Review, 1972 November 10; 1267; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Are in Compliance, 1972 November 12; 792; 1 box (Box 827)
      - These Delegate Slates, 1972 November 12; 793; 26 seconds (Box 827)
      - TV, 1972 November 13; 789; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Election '72-Chronicle, 1972 November 15; 1265; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Here in America: Defense Budget, 1972 November 19; 785; 40 seconds (Box 827)
      - C. Klabunde, 1972 December 4; 55; 3/4-inch 1 box (Box 827)
      - McGovern on the Cavett Show, 1972 December 12; 1173; 1 box (Box 827)
    - 1973-1979, 1973-1984 February 22; 156 boxes
      - Contributor List-Citizens for McGovern Committee-Senate, 1973; 673-674; 2 Boxes (36 diskettes) ) (Box 827)
      - Contributor List-Supplemental, 1973; 676; 14 diskettes (Box 827)
      - McGovern GAO Report/Working Synopsis, 1973 January 25; 53; 3/4-inch 1 box (Box 827)
      - Gridiron Club Dinner, Washington, D.C., 1973 March 10; 1614; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Kimmelman, TV, 1973 April 18; 1480; 1 box (Box 827)
      - CBS TV, 1973 May 5; 1334; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Watergate, 1972 Election, 1973 May 13; 1201; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Redfield Speech, 1973 May 22; 1590; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Today-Gary Hart, 1973 August 1; 1321; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Theodore White with Barry Gray, 1973 August 3; 586; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Theodore White, 1973 August 5-6; 581; 1 box (Box 827)